[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logos by nick.com and
这是尼克和Nick.com的徽标
in this tutorial i'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can take an image and use it to
如何获取图像并将其用于
trace a vector halftone portrait using
使用跟踪向量半色调肖像
inkscape so getting us started here in
Inkscape，让我们从这里开始
inkscape the first thing i want to do is
Inkscape我想做的第一件事是
just set up the workflow so that we all
只需设置工作流程，以便我们所有人
have a similar setup on our screen i'm
在我们的屏幕上有类似的设置，我是
going to come up here to where it says
就会来到这里，上面写着
view
观
i want to make sure i have custom
我想确保我有风俗习惯
selected and then i want to zoom i want
选中，然后我想要进行缩放
to go to view zoom and zoom in at one to
要同时转到查看、缩放和放大，请执行以下操作
one
一
okay now what i'm going to do is i'm
好了，现在我要做的是
going to import my example photo so i
我要导入我的示例照片，这样我
have over here my other my other monitor
把我的另一台显示器拿过来
i have my example photo i'm going to
我有我的样张照片，我要
click and drag that file into inkscape
单击该文件并将其拖到Inkscape中
i'm going to leave the defaults as they
我将保留默认设置
are and click ok and there we go there
然后点击OK，我们就可以开始了
is the example photo i will be using for
是我将使用的示例照片
this tutorial this is just a stock photo
本教程这只是一张库存照片
that i grabbed off the internet i'll
我从互联网上拿来的，我会
have a link in the description of the
在描述中有一个链接
video if you want to use this image
如果您要使用此图像，请播放视频
otherwise you can use whatever image
否则，您可以使用任何图像
you'd like
你会想要
so the first thing we have to do is make
所以我们要做的第一件事就是
this image black and white so i'm going
这张照片是黑白的，所以我要
to make sure i have the image selected
以确保我选择了该图像
and i'll come up here to where it says
我会走到上面写着的地方
filters and i'll come over to color and
滤镜和我会来上色和
i'm looking for grayscale
我在找灰色的
now i'm going to take this menu i'm
现在我要拿着这份菜单我要
going to tick the preview box right here
我要在预览框里打勾
just to give us a preview of how this
只是为了让我们预览一下这是如何
looks uh if you want you can adjust your
看起来，呃，如果你愿意，你可以调整你的
rgb values up here as well as the as the
此处的RGB值以及
uh the lightness i like how this looks
呃，轻盈，我喜欢这个样子
as it is so i'm just going to leave it
因为它是这样的，所以我就不管它了
as it is and click apply
原样，然后单击应用
and now that we've done that now that
现在我们已经做到了这一点
this is applied we can close out of this
这是适用的，我们可以关闭这个
menu and now i want to open up the
菜单，现在我想打开
layers menu which is located
位于的Layers菜单
over here or you can just press ctrl
在这里，或者你可以直接按ctrl键
shift and l on your keyboard
键盘上的Shift和L
so right this right here layer one this
所以就在这里，第一层
is the layer where the image is located
是图像所在的层
we want to create a new layer to trace
我们想要创建一个要追踪的新层
our halftone portrait over this image so
我们在这张图片上的半色调肖像画
i'm going to click the plus icon down
我要向下点击加号图标
here and i'm going to add a new layer
在这里，我要添加一个新的层
i'm going to use the layer name i'm just
我将使用层的名称，我只是
going to leave the default and position
将保留默认设置和位置
we want to make sure we have above
我们想要确保我们有上面的
current and then go ahead and click add
当前，然后继续并单击添加
now what i'm going to do is i'm going to
现在我要做的是我要
create a single circle going over this
在上面画一个圆圈
image right here so let me grab the
图像就在这里，让我拿一下
circles and ellipses tool i'm going to
圆圈和椭圆工具，我要去
click and drag on the canvas to create a
在画布上单击并拖动以创建
circle i'm going to hold ctrl on the
圆圈我要按住Ctrl键
keyboard so it makes a perfectly round
键盘，这样它就能完美地绕个圆圈
circle like that
像这样围成圈
and i'm going to make this black let me
我要让这一切变黑让我
grab the select tool and put this
抓起选择工具，把这个
towards the top of the uh the top left
朝向呃左上角的顶部
corner of the image right here and in
图像的一角就在这里和里面
fact i'm going to scale that down a
事实上，我将把它缩小到一个
little more
再多一点
what i want to do is align this in the
我想要做的是将它与
top left corner here so let's open up
左上角在这里，所以让我们打开
the alignment menu which is over here or
在这里的对齐菜单或
you could press ctrl shift a
您可以按Ctrl Shift a
and with this circle selected i'm going
选择了这个圈子，我要走了
to hold shift and i'm going to click on
按住Shift键，我将点击
the image so we have them both selected
图像，因此我们将它们都选中
and in the align distribute menu i want
在对齐分布菜单中，我希望
to make sure i have last selected chosen
要确保我上次选择了
from this relative drop down and i want
从这个相对的下拉列表中，我想
to align this
要使这一点保持一致
to the left edge and then i want to
向左边缘，然后我想
align this to the top edge so that is
将此与顶边对齐，这样就是
right there in the top left corner and
就在那里的左上角
now we can click off of that to deselect
现在，我们可以单击该选项以取消选择
everything
所有的一切
so now i'm going to click and drag over
所以现在我要点击并拖动到
the circle so i have just the circle
圆圈，所以我只有圆圈
selected and i'm going to go to edit
已选择，我将转到编辑
clone
克隆
create tiled clones
创建平铺克隆
and in this menu over here what we're
在这张菜单上，我们要做的
looking for is
正在寻找的是
the trace option
跟踪选项
now from these settings over here you
现在，从这里的设置中，您可以
want to make sure you have traced the
想要确保您已经跟踪了
drawing under the clone spray items you
画下克隆喷雾物品你
want to have that selected you want to
想要选择您想要的内容
have color selected you want to leave
选择了您要离开的颜色
the defaults as they are over here and
默认设置在这里，并且
then down here we only want presence and
然后在这里我们只想要存在和
size selected we don't want either of
所选的尺码我们都不想要
these selected and then down here apply
这些选择，然后在这里适用
the tiled clones to we want to choose
我们要选择的平铺克隆
width and height and we want to change
宽度和高度，我们想要改变
the width and height to match the width
与宽度匹配的宽度和高度
and height of this image so let me click
以及这张图片的高度，让我点击
on this image here so i can see the
在这张图片上，我可以看到
width and height as you can see the
宽度和高度，如您所见
width is a thousand pixels wide and then
宽度是一千个像素宽，然后
pixels high
像素高
so i'm going to change this over here
所以我要把这个换到这里
let me select the circle again
让我再次选择该圆
i'm going to change this to pixels and
我要将其更改为像素，
i'm going to change this to the same
我要把这个换成同样的
size that uh the images over here which
大小，呃，这里的图像
is 1000 by 778 as you can see i already
是1000乘以778，正如你已经看到的
have it inputted here so once you've
把它输入到这里，这样一旦你
done that you can just go ahead and
做完了，你就可以继续了
click create
单击创建
and as you can see it's going to create
正如你所看到的，它将创造
a bunch of copies of that
一大堆复印件
a bunch of copies of that circle and use
一堆那个圈子的副本，然后用
it to trace over the image here and you
它要在这里和你的图像上进行追踪
can see it a little better if you come
如果你来的话，我能看得更清楚一点
over here to the layers menu and turn
在这里转到层菜单，然后将
off the visibility of layer one you can
关闭第一层的可见性，您可以
see where it traced that image a little
看看它在哪里追踪到了这张图片
better
更好的
now let me turn that back on let me come
现在让我把它打开，让我来
over here let me undo what i just did
在这里，让我撤销我刚刚做的事情
there by pressing ctrl z let me undo it
在那里，按下ctrl z，让我撤销它
again ctrl z one more time ctrl z and
再一次ctrl z再一次ctrl z和
there we go what i want to do is make
我们走吧，我想做的就是
this circle a little smaller and see if
这个圆圈再小一点，看看是否
i can get a better result because i
我可以得到更好的结果，因为我
clicked on the wrong thing let me make
点击了错误的东西让我做出
this a little smaller
这件稍微小一点
click on create
点击Create
and as you can see with the smaller
正如你所看到的较小的
circle it added more circles in here
圆圈在这里加了更多圆圈
there's more circle density so i think
有更多的圆圈密度，所以我认为
that looks a little better if you want
如果你想的话看起来会更好一点
let me undo that again
让我再撤销一次
if you want you can make this larger and
如果你愿意，你可以把它做大一点
see how that looks this is just a matter
看看这看起来怎么样这只是个问题
of personal preference at this point if
在这一点上的个人偏好，如果
you go ahead and click on create you can
您可以继续并单击Create You Can
see how that looks right there i liked
看看这个看起来怎么样，我喜欢
how it looked better with the smaller
更小的看起来如何更好
circle so let me undo that one more time
圆圈，所以让我再来一次
and let me just make that a little
让我把这一点说得有点
smaller like that click on create
更小，点击Create(创建
there we go now i'm going to come over
好了，现在我要过去了
here to the layers menu i'm going to
这里到层菜单，我要去
turn off the visibility of layer one and
关闭第一层的可见性，然后
if you zoom out you can really see the
如果你把镜头缩小，你就能真正看到
portrait it almost looks like an actual
它看起来几乎像是一幅真实的肖像
image but if you zoom in all the way you
图像，但如果你一直放大你
can see this is indeed a vector tracing
可以看出这确实是一种矢量追踪
there is no quality loss here as you
这里没有你这样的质量损失
zoom in these are vectors and the cool
放大这些是矢量和很酷的
thing about this is that all of these
关于这一点，所有这些
circles are linked to the original
圆圈链接到原始
circle so whatever you do to that
所以无论你对它做什么，都要圆圈
original circle will be applied to all
原始圆圈将应用于所有
of the other circles as well let me show
在其他圈子中也让我展示一下
you what i mean i'm going to zoom in
你什么意思我的意思是我要放大
over here i'm going to take this
在这里，我要拿着这个
original circle and move it out of the
原始圆，并将其移出
way
道路
let me zoom out to zoom i'm just holding
让我缩小到我只是拿着的缩放
ctrl and rolling up and down the mouse
Ctrl键并上下滚动鼠标
wheel to move the page around just
方向盘只需移动页面即可
pressing down the mouse wheel and moving
按下鼠标滚轮并移动
the mouse i'm going to take that circle
这只老鼠，我要带上那个圆圈
and i'm going to make that blue
我要把它变成蓝色
and as you can see it made all of the
如你所见，它使所有的
other circles blue and this works with
其他圆圈为蓝色，这适用于
any other transformation as well if i
任何其他转换也一样，如果我
make this a little bigger
把这个做大一点
it's going to make all of those circles
它会让所有这些圆圈
a little bigger and i think that looks
再大一点，我觉得这看起来
better right there up close it looks
更好的是在那里近距离观察
like a tracing of a bunch of little
就像一堆小小的
circles but if you zoom out you can see
圆圈，但如果你缩小，你可以看到
it looks more like a photograph
它看起来更像是一张照片
so i think that should do it for this
所以我认为这应该可以解决这个问题
tutorial that is how you can very easily
这就是教程，你可以很容易地
go about creating your own
着手创建你自己的
halftone portraits using images in
使用中的图像的半色调肖像
inkscape if you have any questions just
Inkscape如果您有任何问题，请
leave a comment below and as always
一如既往地在下面留下评论
thanks for watching
感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]